https://www.shortyspumps.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Log In
Categories
Armstrong PumpBell & GossettHoffman PartsModine PartsReznor PartsWater Heater PartsHVAC ProductsAir FiltersHumidifier Pads and Water PanelsSpecials Featured Products All Products Information
Shipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseSite MapGift Certificate FAQNewsletter Unsubscribe
Important Links
Modine Unite Heater Troubleshooting Manual
Search
(877)821-8770 Toll Free
Home
All Categories
Armstrong PumpBell & GossettHoffman PartsModine PartsReznor PartsWater Heater PartsHVAC ProductsAir FiltersHumidifier Pads and Water Panels
Quick Find
Air Filters
Humidification
Modine Heater Parts
Capacitors
Ignitors
Circuit Boards
Motors
About Us
Account/LoginShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseContact UsNewsletter Unsubscribe
Login
Contact Us
Categories
Armstrong Pump Bell & Gossett Hoffman Parts Modine PartsReznor PartsWater Heater Parts HVAC Products Air Filters Humidifier Pads and Water Panels Specials Featured Products All Products
Manufacturers
Please Select
Amana
Aprilaire
Armstrong
Bell & Gossett
Carrier
Ducane
York
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Privacy Policy Statement
This is the website of Shortys Pumps, a sub-sidary of Shortys HVAC Supplies LLC.
Our business postal address is
P O Box 146
West Newton, IN 46183
The businneses physical address is
7720 Mooresville Rd
West Newton, IN 46183
We can be reached via our main website e-mail at parts@shortyshvac.com
or you can call us on 317-821-8770
For each and every visitor, which comes to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no
information regarding the domain or e-mail address.
We only collect data which is voluntarily provided by the consumer, this would be survey information
and/or site registration data. No information on consumers who solely browse our web page without registration.
With respect to cookies: We do use cookies to store visitors preferences.
If you, the consumer, do not wish to receive e-mails from us in the future, please let us know by
in return, sending an e-mail to us at the above address.
If we supplied by you, with your postal address online during user registration, you will only receive the
information for which you provided us your address.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive
contact from Shortys employees, regarding orders they have placed.
With respect to Ad Servers: We have not partnered with or have any current special relationships
with any ad server companies.
Upon request, we will provide site visitors with access to their own personal information (e.g.,
name, address, phone number).
Our consumers can access their own information by visiting us at https://shortyshvac.com/index.php?main_page=account">https://shortyshvac.com/index.php?main_page=account.
Our consumers can have this information corrected by visiting us at https://shortyshvac.com/index.php?main_page=account">https://shortyshvac.com/index.php?main_page=account.
With respect to security: When it comes to transferring and receiving certain types of sensitive
information, such as financial or health data, we redirect visitors to a very
secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. We have all the
appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against
the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you during registration on our website.
If you feel, at any time, that this website is not following its stated information policy, you may
contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
Back
About Us
Welcome to Shortys Pumps, a division of HVAC Supplies. We are located on the South West side of Indianapolis, IN. Our purpose is to provide Original Equipment Manufacturer parts for the repair and maintenance upkeep of furnaces, air conditioners, ventilation systems and pumps to the general public as well as contractors and commercial building maintenance staff.
Give us a call with the information from your equipment nameplate and we will do our best to help you locate the right paty. We can be reached at our local phone number 317-821-8770, Toll Free 877-821-8770 or by fax at 317-821-8772. Our business hours are 8-5 EST M-F. Prior to making repairs please check your manufacturers instructions and follow all safety precautions. Improper repairs can lead to equipment damage or personal injury or death. If you are unsure of your ability please call a professional to service your equipment.
Trusted
ContactCompany NameShortys Pumps, division of Shortys HVAC SuppliesLocation7720 S Mooresville RDWest Newton, INUSA 46183Get in Touch 877-821-8770 Email Us About Us
Shortys Pumps, division of Shortys HVAC Supplies 2020
